<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>Orland Chamber of Commerce</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 02:59:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Orland History</title>
		<link>/orland-history/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[simon]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 02:59:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=187</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[History Orland, originally called Vermont Settlement and populated by immigrants from Vermont, is the first settlement in Steuben County. Orland celebrates its heritage each year with the Vermont Settlement Festival in late July. After John Stocker, a Vermonter who had been prospecting for his family as well as his neighbors&#8217; families, Orland was settled by &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/orland-history/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Orland History</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>History</p>
<p>Orland, originally called Vermont Settlement and populated by immigrants from Vermont, is the first settlement in Steuben County. Orland celebrates its heritage each year with the Vermont Settlement Festival in late July. After John Stocker, a Vermonter who had been prospecting for his family as well as his neighbors&#8217; families, Orland was settled by John Stocker in 1834. Stocker chose this piece of land due to the abundance of burr-oak opportunities he discovered. Shortly thereafter, pioneers from Windham County, Vermont arrived and built a Baptist Church. [8] In 1837, the town opened a post office. [9]</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-38" src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/800px-Parker_House_Orland_Indiana-268x300.jpg" alt="Orland History 2" width="268" height="300" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/800px-Parker_House_Orland_Indiana-268x300.jpg 268w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/09/800px-Parker_House_Orland_Indiana-768x858.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2019/09/800px-Parker_House_Orland_Indiana.jpg 800w" sizes="(max-width: 268px) 100vw, 268px" title="Orland History 2"></p>
<p>Orland, a stop along the Underground Railroad, was responsible for sheltering and protecting slaves as they made their way to Windsor, Upper Canada, in the years leading up to the Civil War. Russell Brown&#8217;s home was believed to have a second-floor apartment with a separate staircase in which up to 20 slaves could hide. S. U. Clark&#8217;s hotel was also said to have a secret hiding spot behind a basement cupboard. The Butler family south Orland &#8220;fed and shelter scores of them, and then took them to other stations.&#8221; &#8220;[10]</p>
<p>Brown, Clark and Benjamin Waterhouse were all arrested in the lead up to the Civil War for violating the Fugitive Slave Act of1850 at one point or another. Barry and Waterhouse were both convicted. Barry was sentenced to one hour in prison and paid a $30 fine. Other sources have the fine at $1000. [12]</p>
<p>In 1997, the National Register of Historic Places listed Fawn River State Fish Hatchery. [13]</p>
<p>The 2019-20 coronavirus pandemic saw confirmed cases of COVID-19 at a local meat processing facility run by Miller Poultry. This led to sanitation and the introduction of safety measures like temperature checks, social distance, and personal protective equipment. [14]</p>
<p>Geography[edit]</p>
<p>Orland can be found at 41deg43’50’’N 85deg10’11’’W.</p>
<p>According to the 2010 census Orland covers 0.66 square miles (1.71km2) of land. [15]</p>
<p>Demographics[edit]</p>
<p>Historical populationCensusPop.%+-1880416&#8211;1920322&#8211;1930310-3.7%1940307-1.0%195038625.7%19604249.8%19704577.8%1980424-7.2%1990361-14.9%2000341-5.5%201043427.3%2019 (est.)424[4]-2.3%U. S. Decennial Census[16]</p>
<p>2010 census[edit]</p>
<p>The population was 434 as of 2010[3], with 168 households and 117 families. The population density was 657.6 people per square mile (253.9/km2). The average housing unit density was 287.9/square mile (111.2/km2). The town&#8217;s racial makeup was 96.3% White, 1.2% African American and 1.6% from other race. There were 190 housing units at an average density of 287.9 per square mile (111.2/km2). 9.0% of the population was Hispanic/Latino of any race.</p>
<p>There were 168 households. 31.5% of these households had children younger than 18 years old, 53.0% had married couples living together, 10.7% had female householders with no husband, 6.0% had male householders with no wives present, and 30% were non-families. 28.6% of all households consisted of individuals and 14.3% were home to someone 65 years old or older. The average household size was 2.58, and the average family size 3.16.</p>
<p>The median age of residents was 40.2 years. 24% of residents were younger than 18, 9.2% were aged 18-24, 21.4% were between 25-44, 29% were between 45-64, 29% were between 45-64, 16.1% were 65 and older. The town&#8217;s gender composition was 50.0% male, 50.0% female.</p>
<p>2000 census[edit]</p>
<p>According to the 2000 census[5], there were 341 residents, 137 households and 90 families in the town. The average population density was 512.8 per square mile (199.5/km2). At an average density of 230.1 units per square mile (89.5/km2), there were 153 housing units. The town&#8217;s racial composition was 98.83% White with 0.29% Native American and 0.29% Asian. There were 153 housing units at an average density of 230.1 per square mile (89.5/km2). The population was 0.29% Hispanic and Latino of any race.</p>
<p>Orland, Indiana starting with 1876 Atlas</p>
<p>There were 137 households. 34.3% of these households had children under 18 years old, 49.6% had married couples living together, 12.4% were female householders with no husband, and 33.6% weren&#8217;t families. 29.2% of all households consisted of individuals and 13.9% were composed of someone 65 years or older. The average household size was 2.49, and the average family size 3.10.</p>
<p>The town had a spread population with 27.6% of the population under 18 years old, 8.2% of the population aged 18-24, 29.9% of the population aged 25-44, 19.9% of the population aged 45-64, and 14.4% of the population 65 years or older. The median age was 36. There were 100.6 males for every 100 females. There were 93.0 men for every 100 females over 18 years old.</p>
<p>The median income of a household was $38,542 and that of a family was $45,417. The median income for males was $33,438 while that of females was $20,893. The town&#8217;s per capita income was $15,188. The poverty line was reached by 9.2% of households and 7.9% percent of the population. This includes 11.4% of children under 18 years old and 7.7% of people 65 and older.</p>
<p>Education[edit]</p>
<p>The Joyce Public Library is a lending library in the town. [17]</p>
<p>Notable former residents and natives[edit]</p>
<p>Rollie Zeider (1883-1967), Major League Baseball player, 1910-1918. He played for the Chicago White Sox and Chicago Chi-Feds. Cass County was his birthplace. He grew up in Auburn and eventually opened a Garrett restaurant after retiring from baseball. In 1959, he moved to Orland, where he remained until his passing.</p>
<p>Azariah Southworth (May 13th 1986), Television producer/personality 2006.-2008</p>
<p>Andy Lee Graham, &#8220;The Hobo Traveller&#8221;,</p>
<p>Footnotes[edit]</p>
<p>^ &#8220;2019 U. S. Gazetteer Files&#8221;. United States Census Bureau. Retrieved July 16, 2020.</p>
<p>&#8220;US Board on Geographic Names&#8221; United States Geological Survey. 2007-10-25. Retrieved 2008-01-30</p>
<p>Jump up to:</p>
<p>a b &#8220;U.S. Census website&#8221;. United States Census Bureau. Retrieved 2012-12-11.</p>
<p>Jump up to:</p>
<p>a b &#8220;Population and Housing Unit estimates&#8221;. United States Census Bureau. May 24, 2020. Retrieved May 27, 2020.</p>
<p>Jump up to:</p>
<p>a b &#8220;U.S. Census website&#8221; United States Census Bureau. Retrieved 2008-01-30</p>
<p>See Sauer, Indiana DNR.</p>
<p>^ Taylor, et al., p. 26.</p>
<p>Lois Kimball Mathews, page 202: New England expansion: New England settlements and institutions spread to the Mississippi River 1620-1865</p>
<p>^ &#8220;Steuben County&#8221;. Jim Forte Postal History. Retrieved September 29, 2016.</p>
<p>^ Butler.</p>
<p>Indiana Department of Natural Resources Division of Historic Preservation and Archaeology</p>
<p>^ Sauer.</p>
<p>&#8220;National Register Information System&#8221;. National Register of Historic Places. National Park Service. July 9, 2010.</p>
<p>^ Duffy, Jamie (May 2, 2020). &#8220;Steuben meat plant reports positive tests&#8221;. The Journal Gazette</p>
<p>&#8220;G001 – Geographic Identifiers – 2010 Census Summary File 1. United States Census Bureau. Archived from the initial on 2020-02-13. Retrieved 2015-07-17.</p>
<p>&#8220;Census of Population and Housing&#8221;. Census.gov. Retrieved June 4, 2015</p>
<p>&#8220;Indiana Public Library Directory&#8221; (PDF). Indiana State Library. Retrieved 15 March 2018,</p>
<p>References[edit]</p>
<p>Marvin Benjamin Butler (1914). My story about the Civil War, Underground Railroad, United Brethren Publishing Establishment, Huntington, Ind.</p>
<p>Goodspeed, Weston A.</p>
<p>Indiana Department of Natural Resources, &#8220;Underground Railroad Site: Orland&#8221;, August 16, 2008.</p>
<p>Sauer, Lee, &#8220;Freedom Trail&#8221;: The Underground Railroad passed through northeast Indiana. KPC News.net accessed August 18, 2008.</p>
<p>Taylor, Robert M.; Stevens Errol Wayne; Ponder Mary Ann (1990). Indiana: A New Historical Guide. Indiana Historical Society. ISBN 978-0-87195-048-2.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is building information modeling? This is a question which has puzzled many people since long.</title>
		<link>/what-is-building-information-modeling-this-is-a-question-which-has-puzzled-many-people-since-long/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Johnson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 10:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=176</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There are several types of projects, which are undertaken by construction sites so as to build new buildings, bridges, roads, etc.. These projects may also involve changing the structure of the existing buildings and consequently it may be crucial for the construction site to create a virtual model that will help it in knowing the &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/what-is-building-information-modeling-this-is-a-question-which-has-puzzled-many-people-since-long/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">What is building information modeling? This is a question which has puzzled many people since long.</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are several types of projects, which are undertaken by construction sites so as to build new buildings, bridges, roads, etc.. These projects may also involve changing the structure of the existing buildings and consequently it may be crucial for the construction site to create a virtual model that will help it in knowing the many different aspects of the undertaking. This is the main reason why information modeling has been termed as the most important facet of a construction website.</p>
<p>
 It may be said that it is the concept which helps the construction sites in making a digital model that&#8217;s based on a specified set of data and it&#8217;s capable of performing all the operations that are needed for the complete building process. Building information modeling is essentially a computer technology supported by different tools, contracts and software involving the construction site and the production firms that involve the creation and execution of virtual representations of physical and functional characteristics of their physical places. These include everything which concerns the placement of the walls, roof, flooring, etc. which are needed to be assembled in order to construct the building. Building data modeling includes the generation of such models that are used for both architectural function and also for various other purposes like providing support to the engineers in designing the building.</p>
<p>
All this depends on the model that&#8217;s generated from <a href="https://vscenario.com/building-information-modelling/construction-industry/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">building information modeling</a>. The models which are generated through this technology are designed in such a manner so they can be used for different purposes. Additionally, it helps the engineers in evaluating the demands of the construction site and in designing a model accordingly. Building model is generated in such a manner that the design gets more true by considering various factors like the construction site requirements, budget, timeline etc.. When these parameters are considered correctly, the engineers can generate the perfect model that&#8217;s appropriate for the construction site.</p>
<p>
These models are usually generated at a level at which they are not just accurate but also help in saving a great deal of time and money.  Other benefits of building information modeling include decreasing the cost and increasing the precision with the help of the usage of computers, software and other technical equipments such as CAD machines and other applications.</p>
<p>
There are several types of modeling software available on the market which can be utilized for information modeling functions. These applications are specially intended for the purpose of generating information models which are useful for a variety of purposes like constructing virtual models, which may be utilized for construction preparation, which may be used for your evaluation, structure planning, etc.. That is the reason it&#8217;s essential for each and every construction site in order to make use of these programs while building and preparing the building plans.<br />
 </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title></title>
		<link>/174-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Johnson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 06:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=174</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Automobile Transport Services allow you to put your transport needs on the map and also allow your customers know that you are&#8221;busy.&#8221; From load board placards to automobile transportation brochures, a fantastic automobile Transport service permits you to present yourself as an expert in a specific field. It is a good way to impress your &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/174-2/">  Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Automobile Transport Services allow you to put your transport needs on the map and also allow your customers know that you are&#8221;busy.&#8221; From load board placards to automobile transportation brochures, a fantastic automobile Transport service permits you to present yourself as an expert in a specific field. It is a good way to impress your clients and let them know that you are a professional and dependable provider.</p>
<p>Using an auto transport service, it is possible to post your shipping request on their site, connect with motorists on the internet to arrange your transportation, and handle all of the details involved in organizing your vehicle. An automobile transporter manages the details on your own behalf: establishing the date, contacting the motorist, planning the transport, ensuring that it&#8217;s on time, etc.. Once your request is put, you have an choice to pay using a credit card or pay through the website itself. A fantastic automobile transporter also arranges a pickup time and place for your automobile so that you don&#8217;t need to be concerned about doing it. Once your vehicle is at the hands of the Auto</p>
<p>Shipping Company, they could take care of the rest. All you have to do is sit back and relax while the Auto Transporter deals with everything. If you need to call the Automobile Transporter again in the future, it&#8217;s easy to get hold of the rep and reschedule your pickup time or pickup place.<br />
Auto Transport companies provide a wide selection of services, from auto transport to medical transportation to commercial vehicles.</p>
<p>Based on the requirements of their clients, Automobile Transporters can choose to work exclusively with specific industries or they could use a variety of selections to ensure that their customers can receive the very best services possible. If you are having a problem having your vehicle delivered, Automobile Transporters can help you out. Their toll free numbers offer 24-hour customer care, and they have a record of insurance providers in the state of California. This means that when you need to make a claim, you will have the ability to contact the proper person to secure you the very best policy available.</p>
<p>Many Auto Transportation businesses work with their clients to make sure that all of their cars are insured and that any automobile is insured by a policy, even if it is not worth fixing. In the event of an accident, the Auto Transporter will provide all of the coverage you would normally need to repair or replace your car. The Auto Transport firm&#8217;s policies are designed to cover damages brought on by vandalism, theft, fire, or natural disasters, and they often pay for the cost of repairs until you push your vehicle off the lot. Some Auto Transporters have special plans for rental cars, which means that if you need a car that isn&#8217;t damaged by an act of nature, the automobile Transporter can provide one to you in exchange for a refund of the rental payment. Some Auto Transporters even offers insurance for the equipment from the leasing vehicles. This is significant because if you will need to find a car back or when you need the insurance to be revived, you might not want to risk losing the leasing car or the vehicle.</p>
<p>When you have to locate a good Auto Transportation service, there are one by asking around. It can be helpful to shop around to locate a local service which has a good reputation, but you may also use the Internet. There are a number of websites online that list the best services in your area. You can use these websites to find out about the businesses that are presently in company in your area. Also, consider checking with your employer or friends and family.</p>
<p>Automobile Transporters are extremely reliable in that they could get your vehicle to the place that you need it to be and have it waiting for you when you arrive. This can make an extremely stressful situation not as stressful.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Orland Indiana Zip Code</title>
		<link>/orland-indiana-zip-code/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[simon]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 00:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=172</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Contents Orland american legion American legion riders post Popular family-style diner Crowded orland square mall Orland Indiana American Legion Bingo Sep 22, 2017  · orland american legion, Orland, Indiana. 168 likes. Local Business. Jump to. Sections of this page. Accessibility Help. Press alt + / to open this menu. Facebook. Email or Phone: Password: … &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/orland-indiana-zip-code/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Orland Indiana Zip Code</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div style="float: right; padding: 10px; border: 1px solid #ddd; background: #eee;">
<h3>Contents</h3>
<ol>
<li><a href="#orland-american-legion">Orland american legion</a></li>
<li><a href="#american-legion-riders-post">American legion riders post</a></li>
<li><a href="#popular-family-style-diner">Popular family-style diner</a></li>
<li><a href="#crowded-orland-square-mall">Crowded orland square mall</a></li>
</ol>
</div>
<p><a href="/orland-indiana-american-legion-bingo/">Orland Indiana American Legion Bingo</a> Sep 22, 2017  · <span id="orland-american-legion">orland american legion</span>, Orland, Indiana. 168 likes. Local Business. Jump to. Sections of this page. Accessibility Help. Press alt + / to open this menu. Facebook. Email or Phone: Password: … It was my honor and pleasure to join the <span id="american-legion-riders-post">american legion riders post</span> 423 today at their meeting to share the<br />
<a href="/orland-indiana-radar/">Orland Indiana Radar</a> Address For Orland Indiana Orland Community Volunteer Fire Department is located in Orland, IN. View a fire dept photo, logo, contact info, map, volunteer info, mission statement, fire equipment, firefighters and statistics. The <span id="popular-family-style-diner">popular family-style diner</span> has locations on Indianapolis Boulevard in Highland and in Orland Park in Illinois … that’s taken Chicago and other</p>
<p><img class="alignleft" src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/U7u6asGQLoI/hqdefault.jpg?sqp=-oaymwEjCPYBEIoBSFryq4qpAxUIARUAAAAAGAElAADIQj0AgKJDeAE=&amp;rs=AOn4CLDrrd7N3ci5X64WFHDwMlvzNFmkDg" alt="Orland Indiana Vermont Settlement Days Parade Clip 01" title="Orland Indiana Zip Code 4">News about Monday night’s fatal shooting at the <span id="crowded-orland-square-mall">crowded orland square mall</span> spread like wildfire across &#8230; young children to the mall to see Santa Claus. “Guns don’t know ZIP codes. Bullets don’t know &#8230;</p>
<p><a href="/mr-bratz-orland-indiana-hours/">Mr Bratz Orland Indiana Hours</a> Orland Indiana Chamber Of Commerce About the Chamber For over 80 years, The Orland Chamber of Commerce has served as the voice and advocate of the Orland business community. The mission of the Orland Chamber of Commerce is “to serve the greater orland community through leadership and unity as the local business advocate, by promoting<br />
Orland Indiana Ice Cream Shop <a href="/">Orland</a> Indiana Radar Address For Orland Indiana Orland Community Volunteer Fire Department is located in Orland, IN. View a fire dept photo, logo, contact info, map, volunteer info, mission statement, fire equipment, firefighters and statistics. The popular family-style diner has locations on Indianapolis Boulevard in Highland and in Orland Park in Illinois … that’s taken</p>
<p>The massive greater Chicagoland launch will cover more than 4,500 square miles and include more than 200 zip codes in Aurora, Algonquin, Bolingbrook, Bloomingdale, Crystal Lake, Elgin, Flossmoor, &#8230;</p>
<p><a href="/orland-indiana-town-office/">Orland Indiana Town Office</a> Orland Indiana Greenhouse The Garden Shed – 7320 W State Road 120, Orland, Indiana 46776 – Rated 5 based on 56 Reviews &#8220;High quality plants and the staff is super friendly. My… New York mayor bill deblasio says the move will improve health and help reduce greenhouse emissions … will still be able to send</p>
<p>The Chicago metropolitan area contains five out of the ten biggest manufacturing zip codes in the United States &#8230; Mount Prospect, North Barrington, Orland Park, Poplar Grove, Schaumburg, Streamwood, &#8230;</p>
<p><a href="/orland-indiana-chamber-of-commerce/">Orland Indiana Chamber Of Commerce</a> About the Chamber For over 80 years, The Orland Chamber of Commerce has served as the voice and advocate of the Orland business community. The mission of the Orland Chamber of Commerce is “to serve the greater Orland community through leadership and unity as the local business advocate, by promoting quality of life, traditional values</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mr Bratz Orland Indiana Hours</title>
		<link>/mr-bratz-orland-indiana-hours/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[simon]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 22:26:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=171</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Contents Greater orland community Famous hawaiian bratz Musical composition. orland Bill vogel knew American legion riders post 423 Orland Indiana Chamber Of Commerce About the Chamber For over 80 years, The Orland Chamber of Commerce has served as the voice and advocate of the Orland business community. The mission of the Orland Chamber of Commerce &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/mr-bratz-orland-indiana-hours/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Mr Bratz Orland Indiana Hours</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div style="float:right;padding:10px;border:1px solid #ddd;background:#eee">
<h3>Contents</h3>
<ol>
<li><a href="#greater-orland-community">Greater orland community</a></li>
<li><a href="#famous-hawaiian-bratz">Famous hawaiian bratz</a></li>
<li><a href="#musical-composition.-orland">Musical composition. orland</a></li>
<li><a href="#bill-vogel-knew">Bill vogel knew</a></li>
<li><a href="#american-legion-riders-post-423">American legion riders post 423</a></li>
</ol>
</div>
<p><a href="/orland-indiana-chamber-of-commerce/">Orland Indiana Chamber Of Commerce</a> About the Chamber For over 80 years, The Orland Chamber of Commerce has served as the voice and advocate of the Orland business community. The mission of the Orland Chamber of Commerce is “to serve the <span id="greater-orland-community">greater orland community</span> through leadership and unity as the local business advocate, by promoting quality of life, traditional values<br />
<a href="/orland-indiana-radar/">Orland Indiana Radar</a> Address For Orland Indiana Orland Community Volunteer Fire Department is located in Orland, IN. View a fire dept photo, logo, contact info, map, volunteer info, mission statement, fire equipment, firefighters and statistics. The popular family-style diner has locations on Indianapolis Boulevard in Highland and in Orland Park in Illinois &#8230; that&#8217;s taken Chicago and other<br />
<a href="/orland-indiana-town-office/">Orland Indiana Town Office</a> Orland Indiana Greenhouse The Garden Shed &#8211; 7320 W State Road 120, Orland, Indiana 46776 &#8211; Rated 5 based on 56 Reviews &quot;High quality plants and the staff is super friendly. My&#8230; New York mayor bill deblasio says the move will improve health and help reduce greenhouse emissions &#8230; will still be able to send</p>
<p>Mr Bratz specializes in fresh cut Meats we also have lunch meat and cheeses a wide variety of brats along with our <span id="famous-hawaiian-bratz">famous hawaiian bratz</span> we also have homemade salads stop in and check us out History. Established in 2008.</p>
<p><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/tXhOVxe3btk/hqdefault.jpg?sqp=-oaymwEjCPYBEIoBSFryq4qpAxUIARUAAAAAGAElAADIQj0AgKJDeAE=&amp;rs=AOn4CLAheOhdJpxaMz6EMUbwcKAbsM0PbA" alt="252 Orland Indiana" class="alignleft" title="Mr Bratz Orland Indiana Hours 6">Mister Bratz &#8211; 9480 W In-120, Orland, Indiana 46776 &#8211; Rated 5 based on 42 Reviews &quot;This is our second trip to your town to get bratz. We found you last&#8230;</p>
<p>Ludwig, 34, of Orland Park, was swept away by floodwaters &#8230; Search-and-rescue teams descended on Mount Hood. Mr. Ludwig&#8217;s body was found downstream about three hours later, according to the &#8230;</p>
<p><a href="/orland-indiana-ice-cream-shop/">Orland Indiana Ice Cream Shop</a> Orland Indiana Radar Address For Orland Indiana Orland Community Volunteer Fire Department is located in Orland, IN. View a fire dept photo, logo, contact info, map, volunteer info, mission statement, fire equipment, firefighters and statistics. The popular family-style diner has locations on Indianapolis Boulevard in Highland and in Orland Park in Illinois &#8230; that&#8217;s taken</p>
<p>After each section of his statement, Orland repeated the phrase “for that, I am grateful,” as if it were a refrain from a <span id="musical-composition.-orland">musical composition. orland</span> said he had no regrets about the many extra hours &#8230;</p>
<p>Jun 13, 2011 &nbsp;&#183;&#032;Get directions, reviews and information for Mr Bratz in Orland, IN. Mr Bratz 9480 W State Road 120 Orland IN 46776. 10 Reviews (260) 829-6328. Menu &amp; Reservations &#8230; Our friends who live over 2 hours away have stopped to get Bratz here. It is well worth the drive!!! Read more. 07/19/2019 Denise L. Denise L. These brats are amazing! &#8230;</p>
<p><span id="bill-vogel-knew">bill vogel knew</span> just about everyone in town, and because he seemed to thrive on community service since his retirement 11 years ago, he earned the name &quot;Mr. Orland Park &#8230; community because he put in &#8230;</p>
<p>Grown men argued over dolls for six hours as they wrapped up a federal trial pitting &#8230; &quot;In history, there have only been two successful fashion dolls — Barbie and Bratz — and Mr. Larian and Mr.</p>
<p>Find Mr Bratz in Orland with Address, Phone number from Yahoo US Local. Includes Mr Bratz Reviews, maps &amp; directions to Mr Bratz in Orland and more from Yahoo US Local</p>
<p><a href="/orland-indiana-houses-for-sale/">Orland Indiana Houses For Sale</a> Address For Orland Indiana Orland Community Volunteer Fire Department is located in Orland, IN. View a fire dept photo, logo, contact info, map, volunteer info, mission statement, fire equipment, firefighters and statistics. The popular family-style diner has locations on Indianapolis Boulevard in Highland and in Orland Park in Illinois &#8230; that&#8217;s taken Chicago and other</p>
<p>Mister Bratz &#8211; 9480 W In-120, Orland, Indiana 46776 &#8211; Rated 5 based on 42 Reviews &quot;This is our second trip to your town to get bratz. We found you last&#8230;</p>
<p>Mr. Larian had &#8230; who hope to have in Bratz a third arrow in their quiver &#8211; the other two being LOL and MC2. Disclosure: I/we have no positions in any stocks mentioned, and no plans to initiate any &#8230;</p>
<p>“I moved today for a mistrial arguing that Mr. Larian &#8230; the Bratz dolls and accessories made and sold by MGA since 2001 violate Mattel’s copyright on the drawings and sculpts. Shares of Mattel fell &#8230;</p>
<p><a href="/orland-indiana-american-legion-bingo/">Orland Indiana American Legion Bingo</a> Sep 22, 2017 &nbsp;&#183;&#032;Orland American Legion, Orland, Indiana. 168 likes. Local Business. Jump to. Sections of this page. Accessibility Help. Press alt + / to open this menu. Facebook. Email or Phone: Password: &#8230; It was my honor and pleasure to join the <span id="american-legion-riders-post-423">american legion riders post 423</span> today at their meeting to share the</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Orland Indiana American Legion Bingo</title>
		<link>/orland-indiana-american-legion-bingo/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[simon]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 22:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/orland-indiana-american-legion-bingo/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Contents Legion riders post 423 today Longest running parade Indiana radar address Texas hold ’em Chan meditation workshop Sep 22, 2017 &#160;&#183;&#032;Orland American Legion, Orland, Indiana. 168 likes. Local Business. Jump to. Sections of this page. Accessibility Help. Press alt + / to open this menu. Facebook. Email or Phone: Password: &#8230; It was my &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/orland-indiana-american-legion-bingo/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Orland Indiana American Legion Bingo</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div style="float:right;padding:10px;border:1px solid #ddd;background:#eee">
<h3>Contents</h3>
<ol>
<li><a href="#legion-riders-post-423-today">Legion riders post 423 today</a></li>
<li><a href="#longest-running-parade">Longest running parade</a></li>
<li><a href="#indiana-radar-address">Indiana radar address</a></li>
<li><a href="#texas-hold-em">Texas hold ’em</a></li>
<li><a href="#chan-meditation-workshop">Chan meditation workshop</a></li>
</ol>
</div>
<p>Sep 22, 2017 &nbsp;&#183;&#032;Orland American Legion, Orland, Indiana. 168 likes. Local Business. Jump to. Sections of this page. Accessibility Help. Press alt + / to open this menu. Facebook. Email or Phone: Password: &#8230; It was my honor and pleasure to join the American <span id="legion-riders-post-423-today">legion riders post 423 today</span> at their meeting to share the mission of Invisible Vets.</p>
<p>The parade will step off for the 100th time, making it the <span id="longest-running-parade">longest running parade</span> in Indiana, Sept. 2. “The American Legion &#8230;</p>
<p>This information is provided by the Indiana County Tourist Bureau. Times and dates are subject to change. All events are held in Indiana, unless otherwise noted. • Iselin/West Lebanon Fire Department &#8230;</p>
<p><a href="/orland-indiana-ice-cream-shop/">Orland Indiana Ice Cream Shop</a> Orland <span id="indiana-radar-address">indiana radar address</span> For Orland Indiana Orland Community Volunteer Fire Department is located in Orland, IN. View a fire dept photo, logo, contact info, map, volunteer info, mission statement, fire equipment, firefighters and statistics. The popular family-style diner has locations on Indianapolis Boulevard in Highland and in Orland Park in Illinois &#8230; that&#8217;s taken</p>
<p>Born in Greensburg, Indiana to Maurice and Helen Crider &#8230; Upon retirement, Sharon enjoyed golfing, scoring a hole in one, bingo, <span id="texas-hold-em">texas hold ’em</span>, and socializing with her many friends at the American &#8230;</p>
<p>In his newly released book, “Zero to Hero: From Bullied Kid to Warrior” (Pritzker Military Museum &amp; Library), Lynch takes the reader from the working class south suburbs of Chicago and Northwest &#8230;</p>
<p>Burcham Park 200 Indiana St. Celtic Roots Festival, Workshops 1-3:30, Music 4-midnight, Union Pacific Depot, 402 N. 2nd St. Heart <span id="chan-meditation-workshop">chan meditation workshop</span>, 2-3 p.m., Lawrence Public Library, 707 &#8230;</p>
<p><a href="/orland-indiana-radar/">Orland Indiana Radar</a> Address For Orland Indiana Orland Community Volunteer Fire Department is located in Orland, IN. View a fire dept photo, logo, contact info, map, volunteer info, mission statement, fire equipment, firefighters and statistics. The popular family-style diner has locations on Indianapolis Boulevard in Highland and in Orland Park in Illinois &#8230; that&#8217;s taken Chicago and other</p>
<p>American Legion is a Bingo Hall with areas of focus in Bingo Hall. Contact American Legion. American Legion photos, reviews, articles &#8230; Bingo Halls Orland, Indiana 46776-9799 . Send Message &#187; Write a review &#8230; Join Bingo Hall Locator. Sign Up &amp; Get Listed.</p>
<p>Connect and Send Direct Message to American Legion Bingo Hall in Orland, Indiana</p>
<p>The public is welcome for all activities such as 6 p.m. Tuesday bingo &#8230; next fundraiser What: American Legion Post No. 24’s next fundraising event: a meal with proceeds to benefit Columbus-based Our &#8230;</p>
<p>If you have any questions about your LegionSites website application, please contact us via email at support@legionsites.com. All technical support emails will be answered …</p>
<p><a href="/orland-indiana-town-office/">Orland Indiana Town Office</a> Orland Indiana Greenhouse The Garden Shed &#8211; 7320 W State Road 120, Orland, Indiana 46776 &#8211; Rated 5 based on 56 Reviews &quot;High quality plants and the staff is super friendly. My&#8230; New York mayor bill deblasio says the move will improve health and help reduce greenhouse emissions &#8230; will still be able to send</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Orland Indiana Ice Cream Shop</title>
		<link>/orland-indiana-ice-cream-shop/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[simon]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 22:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/orland-indiana-ice-cream-shop/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Contents Byers&#8217; living room Ice cream shop Club.” beloved ice cream Indiana. 5 Steak. american restaurant Basketball. &#8230; east Orland Indiana Radar Address For Orland Indiana Orland Community Volunteer Fire Department is located in Orland, IN. View a fire dept photo, logo, contact info, map, volunteer info, mission statement, fire equipment, firefighters and statistics. The &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/orland-indiana-ice-cream-shop/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Orland Indiana Ice Cream Shop</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div style="float:right;padding:10px;border:1px solid #ddd;background:#eee">
<h3>Contents</h3>
<ol>
<li><a href="#byers-living-room">Byers&#8217; living room</a></li>
<li><a href="#ice-cream-shop">Ice cream shop</a></li>
<li><a href="#club.-beloved-ice-cream">Club.” beloved ice cream</a></li>
<li><a href="#indiana.-5">Indiana. 5</a></li>
<li><a href="#steak.-american-restaurant">Steak. american restaurant</a></li>
<li><a href="#basketball.-...-east">Basketball. &#8230; east</a></li>
</ol>
</div>
<p><a href="/orland-indiana-radar/">Orland Indiana Radar</a> Address For Orland Indiana Orland Community Volunteer Fire Department is located in Orland, IN. View a fire dept photo, logo, contact info, map, volunteer info, mission statement, fire equipment, firefighters and statistics. The popular family-style diner has locations on Indianapolis Boulevard in Highland and in Orland Park in Illinois &#8230; that&#8217;s taken Chicago and other</p>
<p>Guests can pose with Demogorgon in Will <span id="byers-living-room">byers&#8217; living room</span> from season one and snack on something sweet at the Scoops Ahoy &#8230;</p>
<p>He didn’t see another <span id="ice-cream-shop">ice cream shop</span>, the kind that offered the distinct flavors he &#8230; Cervera, after studying business at Indiana University South Bend, is applying what he learned in the business &#8230;</p>
<p><a href="/orland-indiana-houses-for-sale/">Orland Indiana Houses For Sale</a> Address For Orland Indiana Orland Community Volunteer Fire Department is located in Orland, IN. View a fire dept photo, logo, contact info, map, volunteer info, mission statement, fire equipment, firefighters and statistics. The popular family-style diner has locations on Indianapolis Boulevard in Highland and in Orland Park in Illinois &#8230; that&#8217;s taken Chicago and other</p>
<p>Students from nearby Taylor University and Indiana Wesleyan University enjoy trying to try every flavor to make their “100 <span id="club.-beloved-ice-cream">club.” beloved ice cream</span> shop Snookies has a been a favorite among Des Moines &#8230;</p>
<p><a href="/orland-indiana-greenhouse/">Orland Indiana Greenhouse</a> The Garden Shed &#8211; 7320 W State Road 120, Orland, Indiana 46776 &#8211; Rated 5 based on 56 Reviews &quot;High quality plants and the staff is super friendly. My&#8230; New York mayor bill deblasio says the move will improve health and help reduce greenhouse emissions &#8230; will still be able to send them to school<br />
<a href="/orland-indiana-town-office/">Orland Indiana Town Office</a> Orland Indiana Greenhouse The Garden Shed &#8211; 7320 W State Road 120, Orland, Indiana 46776 &#8211; Rated 5 based on 56 Reviews &quot;High quality plants and the staff is super friendly. My&#8230; New York mayor bill deblasio says the move will improve health and help reduce greenhouse emissions &#8230; will still be able to send</p>
<p>GREENWOOD — A Greenwood ice cream shop has removed its former owner from state documents reflecting the business’s leadership. John Cassin of Whiteland is facing two counts of child pornography &#8230;</p>
<p>on any given weekend, there’s a good chance you’ve seen the long lines outside Sub Zero Nitrogen Ice Cream shop. The store isn’t local to Indianapolis, but Sub Zero Indiana manager John Einsfeld says &#8230;</p>
<p>Ice Cream Shop in Orland, <span id="indiana.-5">indiana. 5</span>. 5 out of 5 stars. Community See All. 211 people like this. 211 people follow this. About See All. 9495 Main St Orland, Indiana 46776. Contact Sweet Summers on Messenger. Ice Cream Shop &#183; Bakery. Price Range $$ Page Transparency See More.</p>
<p>Sep 01, 2019 &nbsp;&#183;&#032;Ice Cream Shop &#183; 7 tips and reviews Brandon Register-Watford: The original in Hollywood CA. offered a soda shoppe and ice cream parlour and lunch counter in addition to being a pharmacy. Legendary actress Lana Turner was discovered here while having lunch.</p>
<p><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/dMDMkgp4MII/hqdefault.jpg?sqp=-oaymwEjCPYBEIoBSFryq4qpAxUIARUAAAAAGAElAADIQj0AgKJDeAE=&amp;rs=AOn4CLA47u05pgiiJOEszzHspkIzgaucGA" alt="Diana Pretend Play Ice Cream Shop" class="alignleft" title="Orland Indiana Ice Cream Shop 8">Orland,Indiana Cruise-In. 272 likes &#183; 5 talking about this. Cool people sharing their Cool cars, &#8230; Ice Cream Shop. Chubby&#8217;s Fish and <span id="steak.-american-restaurant">steak. american restaurant</span>. Prairie Heights Boys <span id="basketball.-...-east">basketball. &#8230; east</span> edge of Orland on State Road 120 at Bunches grocery is 900 West , South 5 miles to 150 North. On the corner.</p>
<p><a href="/address-for-orland-indiana/">Address For Orland Indiana</a> Orland Community Volunteer Fire Department is located in Orland, IN. View a fire dept photo, logo, contact info, map, volunteer info, mission statement, fire equipment, firefighters and statistics. The popular family-style diner has locations on Indianapolis Boulevard in Highland and in Orland Park in Illinois &#8230; that&#8217;s taken Chicago and other cities by storm —<br />
<a href="/orland-indiana-chamber-of-commerce/">Orland Indiana Chamber Of Commerce</a> About the Chamber For over 80 years, The Orland Chamber of Commerce has served as the voice and advocate of the Orland business community. The mission of the Orland Chamber of Commerce is “to serve the greater Orland community through leadership and unity as the local business advocate, by promoting quality of life, traditional values</p>
<p>“We just kind of tried to think of stuff that was Indiana summer,” Melanie Miles said. Mint chocolate chip is made with fresh mint and blueberry buttermilk contains local blueberries at at Cone + &#8230;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Orland Indiana Town Office</title>
		<link>/orland-indiana-town-office/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[simon]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 19:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/orland-indiana-town-office/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Contents Orland community volunteer fire Impacting central indiana farmers Orland town office Office approved felony charges Orland Indiana Greenhouse The Garden Shed &#8211; 7320 W State Road 120, Orland, Indiana 46776 &#8211; Rated 5 based on 56 Reviews &#34;High quality plants and the staff is super friendly. My&#8230; New York mayor bill deblasio says the &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/orland-indiana-town-office/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Orland Indiana Town Office</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div style="float:right;padding:10px;border:1px solid #ddd;background:#eee">
<h3>Contents</h3>
<ol>
<li><a href="#orland-community-volunteer-fire">Orland community volunteer fire</a></li>
<li><a href="#impacting-central-indiana-farmers">Impacting central indiana farmers</a></li>
<li><a href="#orland-town-office">Orland town office</a></li>
<li><a href="#office-approved-felony-charges">Office approved felony charges</a></li>
</ol>
</div>
<p><a href="/orland-indiana-greenhouse/">Orland Indiana Greenhouse</a> The Garden Shed &#8211; 7320 W State Road 120, Orland, Indiana 46776 &#8211; Rated 5 based on 56 Reviews &quot;High quality plants and the staff is super friendly. My&#8230; New York mayor bill deblasio says the move will improve health and help reduce greenhouse emissions &#8230; will still be able to send them to school<br />
<a href="/address-for-orland-indiana/">Address For Orland Indiana</a> <span id="orland-community-volunteer-fire">orland community volunteer fire</span> Department is located in Orland, IN. View a fire dept photo, logo, contact info, map, volunteer info, mission statement, fire equipment, firefighters and statistics. The popular family-style diner has locations on Indianapolis Boulevard in Highland and in Orland Park in Illinois &#8230; that&#8217;s taken Chicago and other cities by storm —</p>
<p>Town of Orland, Indiana, Orland, Indiana. 595 likes &#183; 135 talking about this. The Town of Orland welcomes all to our beautiful town. Town Council is&#8230;</p>
<p>The Town of Orland was incorporated in 1800, formerly known as &quot;Plantation #2&quot; on the east side of the Penobscot River. As of the year 2010, the population was 2,225 people. Download the Orland Town Report, 2017-2018 (1.5 MB, PDF) The Town of Orland now …</p>
<p><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/4D96rkCNDR4/hqdefault.jpg?sqp=-oaymwEjCPYBEIoBSFryq4qpAxUIARUAAAAAGAElAADIQj0AgKJDeAE=&amp;rs=AOn4CLB-TNx5oNvxpHQNMyqUnBLBMktXIg" alt="Orland Indiana Vermont Settlement Days Parade Clip 02" class="alignleft" title="Orland Indiana Town Office 10">Orland Park officials approved permitting video &#8230; &quot;It&#8217;s too early to tell the effects on our town.&quot; Trustee Jim Dodge &#8230;</p>
<p>A man died after being pulled from an SUV following a crash Sunday evening in southwest suburban Orland Park. About 6 p.m., a &#8230; the medical examiner’s office said. The driver of the Town and Country &#8230;</p>
<p>The town established a post office in 1837. In the decades leading up to the Civil War, Orland was a stop on the Underground Railroad, sheltering and protecting runaway slaves until they could complete the journey to Windsor, Upper Canada. The home of Russell Brown was said to contain a secret apartment on the second floor, complete with a &#8230;</p>
<p><a href="/orland-indiana-radar/">Orland Indiana Radar</a> Address For Orland Indiana Orland Community Volunteer Fire Department is located in Orland, IN. View a fire dept photo, logo, contact info, map, volunteer info, mission statement, fire equipment, firefighters and statistics. The popular family-style diner has locations on Indianapolis Boulevard in Highland and in Orland Park in Illinois &#8230; that&#8217;s taken Chicago and other</p>
<p>Orland is a town located in the northwest corner of Steuben County, Indiana in Millgrove Township at the intersection of State Road 120 and State Road 327. The population was 434 at the 2010 census. Orland was founded by John Stocker. Orland is recognized as the first settlement in Steuben County, populated by immigrants from Vermont and &#8230;</p>
<p>The Town of Orland would like to thank YOU our town residents for keeping your homes &amp; yards looking beautiful!! The Town was in top shape during the Orland Vermont Settlement festival and a big part of that was our residents taking pride in their own homes and yards for this event!</p>
<p><a href="/orland-indiana-chamber-of-commerce/">Orland Indiana Chamber Of Commerce</a> About the Chamber For over 80 years, The Orland Chamber of Commerce has served as the voice and advocate of the Orland business community. The mission of the Orland Chamber of Commerce is “to serve the greater Orland community through leadership and unity as the local business advocate, by promoting quality of life, traditional values<br />
<a href="/orland-indiana-houses-for-sale/">Orland Indiana Houses For Sale</a> Address For Orland Indiana Orland Community Volunteer Fire Department is located in Orland, IN. View a fire dept photo, logo, contact info, map, volunteer info, mission statement, fire equipment, firefighters and statistics. The popular family-style diner has locations on Indianapolis Boulevard in Highland and in Orland Park in Illinois &#8230; that&#8217;s taken Chicago and other<br />
<a href="/orland-indiana-christmas-tree-farm/">Orland Indiana Christmas Tree Farm</a> If you prefer a real tree for Christmas, you may be spending a little more money this year because of a shortage <span id="impacting-central-indiana-farmers">impacting central indiana farmers</span> &#8230; David Jay, owner of Jay’s Christmas Tree Farm in &#8230; Southern Indiana Christmas is right around the corner, which means it&#8217;s time to starting thinking about your tree.</p>
<p>This business operation is involved in Government Offices &#8211; City, Village &amp; Town as well as other possible related aspects and functions of Government Offices &#8211; City, Village &amp; Town. In Orland Maine 4472 <span id="orland-town-office">orland town office</span> maintains its local business operations and may accomplish other local business operations outside of Orland in additional &#8230;</p>
<p>ORLAND &#8230; Route 1 and the center of town on the Old County Road. Many of the town’s organizations take part, including the scouts, the local United Methodist church, the historical society and the &#8230;</p>
<p>The Will County State’s Attorney’s <span id="office-approved-felony-charges">office approved felony charges</span> of aggravated battery &#8230; STOLEN CAR: Police discovered a &#8230;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Orland Indiana Radar</title>
		<link>/orland-indiana-radar/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[simon]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 19:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/orland-indiana-radar/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Contents 2 meteorologist mary kay kleist Rated 5 based Reduce greenhouse emissions Forecast. access hourly Orland business community Local business advocate Address For Orland Indiana Orland Community Volunteer Fire Department is located in Orland, IN. View a fire dept photo, logo, contact info, map, volunteer info, mission statement, fire equipment, firefighters and statistics. The popular &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/orland-indiana-radar/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Orland Indiana Radar</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div style="float:right;padding:10px;border:1px solid #ddd;background:#eee">
<h3>Contents</h3>
<ol>
<li><a href="#meteorologist-mary-kay-kleist">2 meteorologist mary kay kleist</a></li>
<li><a href="#rated-5-based">Rated 5 based</a></li>
<li><a href="#reduce-greenhouse-emissions">Reduce greenhouse emissions</a></li>
<li><a href="#forecast.-access-hourly">Forecast. access hourly</a></li>
<li><a href="#orland-business-community">Orland business community</a></li>
<li><a href="#local-business-advocate">Local business advocate</a></li>
</ol>
</div>
<p><a href="/address-for-orland-indiana/">Address For Orland Indiana</a> Orland Community Volunteer Fire Department is located in Orland, IN. View a fire dept photo, logo, contact info, map, volunteer info, mission statement, fire equipment, firefighters and statistics. The popular family-style diner has locations on Indianapolis Boulevard in Highland and in Orland Park in Illinois &#8230; that&#8217;s taken Chicago and other cities by storm —</p>
<p>Sep 07, 2019 &nbsp;&#183;&#032;Maps &amp; Radar Severe Weather News &amp; Blogs Mobile Apps More Sensor Network Maps &amp; Radar &#8230; Orland, IN star_ratehome. 67 F Angola Station | …</p>
<p><a href="/orland-indiana-houses-for-sale/">Orland Indiana Houses For Sale</a> Address For Orland Indiana Orland Community Volunteer Fire Department is located in Orland, IN. View a fire dept photo, logo, contact info, map, volunteer info, mission statement, fire equipment, firefighters and statistics. The popular family-style diner has locations on Indianapolis Boulevard in Highland and in Orland Park in Illinois &#8230; that&#8217;s taken Chicago and other</p>
<p>6 minutes ago CBS 2 Weather Watch 10 p.m. 8-28-19CBS <span id="meteorologist-mary-kay-kleist">2 meteorologist mary kay kleist</span> has the latest extended forecast &#8230;</p>
<p>12 minutes ago CBS 2 Weather Watch 5 p.m. 8-28-19CBS 2 meteorologist Mary Kay Kleist has the forecast &#8230; 2 hours ago Tragedy &#8230;</p>
<p><a href="/orland-indiana-greenhouse/">Orland Indiana Greenhouse</a> The Garden Shed &#8211; 7320 W State Road 120, Orland, Indiana 46776 &#8211; <span id="rated-5-based">rated 5 based</span> on 56 Reviews &quot;High quality plants and the staff is super friendly. My&#8230; New York mayor bill deblasio says the move will improve health and help <span id="reduce-greenhouse-emissions">reduce greenhouse emissions</span> &#8230; will still be able to send them to school</p>
<p><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/tXhOVxe3btk/hqdefault.jpg?sqp=-oaymwEjCPYBEIoBSFryq4qpAxUIARUAAAAAGAElAADIQj0AgKJDeAE=&amp;rs=AOn4CLAheOhdJpxaMz6EMUbwcKAbsM0PbA" alt="252 Orland Indiana" class="alignleft" title="Orland Indiana Radar 12">Get the Orland weather <span id="forecast.-access-hourly">forecast. access hourly</span>, 10 day and 15 day forecasts along with up to the minute reports and videos for Orland, IN 46776 from AccuWeather.com</p>
<p>Alberta is forecast to post the slowest growth of any region in Canada this year. The situation isn&#8217;t likely to improve any &#8230;</p>
<p><a href="/orland-indiana-chamber-of-commerce/">Orland Indiana Chamber Of Commerce</a> About the Chamber For over 80 years, The Orland Chamber of Commerce has served as the voice and advocate of the <span id="orland-business-community">orland business community</span>. The mission of the Orland Chamber of Commerce is “to serve the greater Orland community through leadership and unity as the <span id="local-business-advocate">local business advocate</span>, by promoting quality of life, traditional values</p>
<p>Orland Volunteers in Police Service (VIPS) hosts the National Night Out event each year and representatives from law enforcement agencies, ambulance services, fire, public safety, health organizations &#8230;</p>
<p>Thank you for reporting this station. We will review the data in question. You are about to report this weather station for bad data. Please select the information that is incorrect.</p>
<p>See the latest Orland Doppler weather radar map including areas of rain, snow and ice on AccuWeather.com. See the latest Orland Doppler weather radar map …</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Orland Indiana Chamber Of Commerce</title>
		<link>/orland-indiana-chamber-of-commerce/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[simon]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 19:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/orland-indiana-chamber-of-commerce/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Contents Orland park area Orland community volunteer fire Angola american legion Northeast indiana woodworkers About the Chamber For over 80 years, The Orland Chamber of Commerce has served as the voice and advocate of the Orland business community. The mission of the Orland Chamber of Commerce is “to serve the greater Orland community through leadership &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/orland-indiana-chamber-of-commerce/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Orland Indiana Chamber Of Commerce</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div style="float:right;padding:10px;border:1px solid #ddd;background:#eee">
<h3>Contents</h3>
<ol>
<li><a href="#orland-park-area">Orland park area</a></li>
<li><a href="#orland-community-volunteer-fire">Orland community volunteer fire</a></li>
<li><a href="#angola-american-legion">Angola american legion</a></li>
<li><a href="#northeast-indiana-woodworkers">Northeast indiana woodworkers</a></li>
</ol>
</div>
<p>About the Chamber For over 80 years, The Orland Chamber of Commerce has served as the voice and advocate of the Orland business community. The mission of the Orland Chamber of Commerce is “to serve the greater Orland community through leadership and unity as the local business advocate, by promoting quality of life, traditional values and economic opportunities within the community.”</p>
<p><a href="/vermont-settlement-days-orland-indiana-2019/">Vermont Settlement Days Orland Indiana 2019</a> Orland Indiana Grocery Stores Realty Income picked up another Mariano’s grocery store, this time paying $36.1 million for the chain’s Orland Park location. The San Diego-based real estate investment trust in late march acquired &#8230; The one and only Albright&#8217;s Grocery Store &#8211; Corunna, indiana orland indiana Post Office Hours The first four locations &#8230;</p>
<p>Orland Area Chamber of Commerce, Orland, California. 789 likes. The Orland Chamber of Commerce supports and promotes local businesses.</p>
<p>Andy’s Frozen Custard opens in Orland Park Missouri-based Andy’s Frozen Custard &#8230; Real estate company. The Mokena Chamber of Commerce has also moved to its new location at 11104 Front St., Unit 1B.</p>
<p><a href="/orland-indiana-christmas-tree-farm/">Orland Indiana Christmas Tree Farm</a> If you prefer a real tree for Christmas, you may be spending a little more money this year because of a shortage impacting central indiana farmers &#8230; David Jay, owner of Jay’s Christmas Tree Farm in &#8230; Southern Indiana Christmas is right around the corner, which means it&#8217;s time to starting thinking about your tree.</p>
<p>Orland Chamber of Commerce. 374 likes. The Orland Chamber serves the businesses and community of Orland, IN.</p>
<p><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/U7u6asGQLoI/hqdefault.jpg?sqp=-oaymwEjCPYBEIoBSFryq4qpAxUIARUAAAAAGAElAADIQj0AgKJDeAE=&amp;rs=AOn4CLDrrd7N3ci5X64WFHDwMlvzNFmkDg" alt="Orland Indiana Vermont Settlement Days Parade Clip 01" class="alignleft" title="Orland Indiana Chamber Of Commerce 14">Find Trusted Businesses in Orland, Indiana. Business Directory Orland. Latest Activity</p>
<p>PORTAGE │ Taxes, education, energy, environmental, government reform and labor policy were topics addressed by representatives of the Indiana Chamber of Commerce during a legislative preview for local &#8230;</p>
<p>McLaughlin to Deliver State of Orland Park Orland Park Mayor Dan McLaughlin will give his state of the village address to the <span id="orland-park-area">orland park area</span> Chamber of Commerce breakfast meeting &#8230; The Illinois &#8230;</p>
<p>Sponsoring partners for the Southwest Expo are the Orland Park Area Chamber of Commerce, Chicago Southland Chamber of Commerce, Chicago Southland Convention &amp; Visitors Bureau, Tinley Park Chamber of &#8230;</p>
<p><a href="/orland-indiana-houses-for-sale/">Orland Indiana Houses For Sale</a> Address For Orland Indiana <span id="orland-community-volunteer-fire">orland community volunteer fire</span> Department is located in Orland, IN. View a fire dept photo, logo, contact info, map, volunteer info, mission statement, fire equipment, firefighters and statistics. The popular family-style diner has locations on Indianapolis Boulevard in Highland and in Orland Park in Illinois &#8230; that&#8217;s taken Chicago and other<br />
<a href="/orland-indiana-greenhouse/">Orland Indiana Greenhouse</a> The Garden Shed &#8211; 7320 W State Road 120, Orland, Indiana 46776 &#8211; Rated 5 based on 56 Reviews &quot;High quality plants and the staff is super friendly. My&#8230; New York mayor bill deblasio says the move will improve health and help reduce greenhouse emissions &#8230; will still be able to send them to school</p>
<p>INDIANAPOLIS (AP) — Indiana Republican voters chose Rep &#8230; 2-to-1 edge in fundraising while racking up endorsements from groups such as the U.S. Chamber of Commerce. He also received financial &#8230;</p>
<p>A ribbon cutting is set for 11:15 a.m. with the Orland Park Chamber of Commerce. The Chicago-area company was founded &#8230; It has a second showroom in Highland in northwest Indiana. It features a large &#8230;</p>
<p><a href="/address-for-orland-indiana/">Address For Orland Indiana</a> Orland Community Volunteer Fire Department is located in Orland, IN. View a fire dept photo, logo, contact info, map, volunteer info, mission statement, fire equipment, firefighters and statistics. The popular family-style diner has locations on Indianapolis Boulevard in Highland and in Orland Park in Illinois &#8230; that&#8217;s taken Chicago and other cities by storm —</p>
<p>Chamber of Commerce. Chamber of Commerce. Sorry, no content matched your criteria.</p>
<p><a href="/orland-indiana-legion/">Orland Indiana Legion</a> Maumee St., Angola, 6:30 p.m. • <span id="angola-american-legion">angola american legion</span> post No. 31 &#8230; John St., Angola, 6 p.m. • <span id="northeast-indiana-woodworkers">northeast indiana woodworkers</span>, Presbyterian Chapel of the Lakes, 2955 W. Orland Road, Angola, 7 p.m. • &#8230; Orland Indiana Grocery Stores Realty Income picked up another Mariano’s grocery store, this time paying $36.1 million for the</p>
<p>Contact the Chamber office at 708-349-9272. The Orland Park Area Chamber of Commerce is dedicated to be the primary resource helping business and the community grow and prosper.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
