<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	 xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" >

<channel>
	<title>Peter Johnson &#8211; Orland Chamber of Commerce</title>
	<atom:link href="/author/peter/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 20:38:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>What is building information modeling? This is a question which has puzzled many people since long.</title>
		<link>/what-is-building-information-modeling-this-is-a-question-which-has-puzzled-many-people-since-long/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Johnson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 10:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=176</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There are several types of projects, which are undertaken by construction sites so as to build new buildings, bridges, roads, etc.. These projects may also involve changing the structure of the existing buildings and consequently it may be crucial for the construction site to create a virtual model that will help it in knowing the &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/what-is-building-information-modeling-this-is-a-question-which-has-puzzled-many-people-since-long/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">What is building information modeling? This is a question which has puzzled many people since long.</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are several types of projects, which are undertaken by construction sites so as to build new buildings, bridges, roads, etc.. These projects may also involve changing the structure of the existing buildings and consequently it may be crucial for the construction site to create a virtual model that will help it in knowing the many different aspects of the undertaking. This is the main reason why information modeling has been termed as the most important facet of a construction website.</p>
<p>
 It may be said that it is the concept which helps the construction sites in making a digital model that&#8217;s based on a specified set of data and it&#8217;s capable of performing all the operations that are needed for the complete building process. Building information modeling is essentially a computer technology supported by different tools, contracts and software involving the construction site and the production firms that involve the creation and execution of virtual representations of physical and functional characteristics of their physical places. These include everything which concerns the placement of the walls, roof, flooring, etc. which are needed to be assembled in order to construct the building. Building data modeling includes the generation of such models that are used for both architectural function and also for various other purposes like providing support to the engineers in designing the building.</p>
<p>
All this depends on the model that&#8217;s generated from <a href="https://vscenario.com/building-information-modelling/construction-industry/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">building information modeling</a>. The models which are generated through this technology are designed in such a manner so they can be used for different purposes. Additionally, it helps the engineers in evaluating the demands of the construction site and in designing a model accordingly. Building model is generated in such a manner that the design gets more true by considering various factors like the construction site requirements, budget, timeline etc.. When these parameters are considered correctly, the engineers can generate the perfect model that&#8217;s appropriate for the construction site.</p>
<p>
These models are usually generated at a level at which they are not just accurate but also help in saving a great deal of time and money.  Other benefits of building information modeling include decreasing the cost and increasing the precision with the help of the usage of computers, software and other technical equipments such as CAD machines and other applications.</p>
<p>
There are several types of modeling software available on the market which can be utilized for information modeling functions. These applications are specially intended for the purpose of generating information models which are useful for a variety of purposes like constructing virtual models, which may be utilized for construction preparation, which may be used for your evaluation, structure planning, etc.. That is the reason it&#8217;s essential for each and every construction site in order to make use of these programs while building and preparing the building plans.<br />
 </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title></title>
		<link>/174-2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter Johnson]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 06:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=174</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Automobile Transport Services allow you to put your transport needs on the map and also allow your customers know that you are&#8221;busy.&#8221; From load board placards to automobile transportation brochures, a fantastic automobile Transport service permits you to present yourself as an expert in a specific field. It is a good way to impress your &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/174-2/">  Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Automobile Transport Services allow you to put your transport needs on the map and also allow your customers know that you are&#8221;busy.&#8221; From load board placards to automobile transportation brochures, a fantastic automobile Transport service permits you to present yourself as an expert in a specific field. It is a good way to impress your clients and let them know that you are a professional and dependable provider.</p>
<p>Using an auto transport service, it is possible to post your shipping request on their site, connect with motorists on the internet to arrange your transportation, and handle all of the details involved in organizing your vehicle. An automobile transporter manages the details on your own behalf: establishing the date, contacting the motorist, planning the transport, ensuring that it&#8217;s on time, etc.. Once your request is put, you have an choice to pay using a credit card or pay through the website itself. A fantastic automobile transporter also arranges a pickup time and place for your automobile so that you don&#8217;t need to be concerned about doing it. Once your vehicle is at the hands of the Auto</p>
<p>Shipping Company, they could take care of the rest. All you have to do is sit back and relax while the Auto Transporter deals with everything. If you need to call the Automobile Transporter again in the future, it&#8217;s easy to get hold of the rep and reschedule your pickup time or pickup place.<br />
Auto Transport companies provide a wide selection of services, from auto transport to medical transportation to commercial vehicles.</p>
<p>Based on the requirements of their clients, Automobile Transporters can choose to work exclusively with specific industries or they could use a variety of selections to ensure that their customers can receive the very best services possible. If you are having a problem having your vehicle delivered, Automobile Transporters can help you out. Their toll free numbers offer 24-hour customer care, and they have a record of insurance providers in the state of California. This means that when you need to make a claim, you will have the ability to contact the proper person to secure you the very best policy available.</p>
<p>Many Auto Transportation businesses work with their clients to make sure that all of their cars are insured and that any automobile is insured by a policy, even if it is not worth fixing. In the event of an accident, the Auto Transporter will provide all of the coverage you would normally need to repair or replace your car. The Auto Transport firm&#8217;s policies are designed to cover damages brought on by vandalism, theft, fire, or natural disasters, and they often pay for the cost of repairs until you push your vehicle off the lot. Some Auto Transporters have special plans for rental cars, which means that if you need a car that isn&#8217;t damaged by an act of nature, the automobile Transporter can provide one to you in exchange for a refund of the rental payment. Some Auto Transporters even offers insurance for the equipment from the leasing vehicles. This is significant because if you will need to find a car back or when you need the insurance to be revived, you might not want to risk losing the leasing car or the vehicle.</p>
<p>When you have to locate a good Auto Transportation service, there are one by asking around. It can be helpful to shop around to locate a local service which has a good reputation, but you may also use the Internet. There are a number of websites online that list the best services in your area. You can use these websites to find out about the businesses that are presently in company in your area. Also, consider checking with your employer or friends and family.</p>
<p>Automobile Transporters are extremely reliable in that they could get your vehicle to the place that you need it to be and have it waiting for you when you arrive. This can make an extremely stressful situation not as stressful.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
